<resources>
    <string name="app_name">World cup Russia 2018 - Teams, Players &amp; Stats</string>
    <string name="wiki"><u>Wiki</u></string>

    <string name="ronldomessilist">&#42; Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo both will try their best for the Glory in Russia 2018\n&#42; They will be 35 and 37 at Qatar 2022 respectively\n&#42; So, theoretically this is their last shot for FIFA World Cup Glory\n
    </string>
    <string name="frstslidequote">"Lionel Messi doesnt have the energy he had when he was 20 years old, nor does he have a magic wand to ensure his team qualifies. He has lost spontaneity and strength in his dribbling.”\n\nRaymond Domenech, 8 March 2017\n
    "There were times when Cristiano Ronaldo’s team led 4-0 and he still wanted to score two goals so badly… But thats over now."\n\nBernd Schuster, 11 April 2017</string>
    <string name="frstslidebelow"><b>Messi on 9 March 2017:</b> Scores one and is instrumental in two more as Barcelona beat Paris Saint-Germain 6-1, making UEFA Champions League history.
        \n\n<b>Ronaldo on 18 April 2018:</b> Scores in his 13th successive game, netting his 24th goal during that period.
    \n\nPeople have wanted to be the first to flag the end of the Messi and Ronaldo dynasties for some time. When staggering performances have been handed out on a near-weekly basis for over a decade, a fallow month can seem like an eternity.\n\n
However, with the pair still on top of Spains La Liga scoring charts, and Ronaldo leading the way in the Champions League, their supremacy is far from over. But, at 30 and 33 respectively, time is inevitably running out for the pair to add the FIFA World Cup™ to their heaving trophy cabinets.\n\n
With both heading to their fourth finals, will they find success in Russia, and what are their hopes should they not be standing at the top of the podium on 15 July?\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="frtsslidelast"><u><b>This season</b></u>
        \n<b>Cristiano Ronaldo (Real Madrid and Portugal)</b>\n
Appearances: 47\n
Goals: 48\n
Assists: 10\n
Achievements: FIFA Club World Cup 2017 winner, Spanish Supercopa winner, UEFA Super Cup winner, UEFA Champions League finalist\n
\n<b>Lionel Messi (Barcelona and Argentina)</b>\n
Appearances: 56\n
Goals: 46\n
Assists: 18\n
Achievements: La Liga winner, Copa del Rey winner</string>

    <string name="frstslidelastttt">
        \n<b>Where they have fallen before\n</b>
<b>Ronaldo</b>\n
2006: Semi-final, 1-0 v France\n
2010: Round of 16, 1-0 v Spain\n
2014: Group stage\n
<b>Messi</b>\n
2006: Quarter-final, 1-1 (4-2 PSO) v Germany\n
2010: Quarter-final, 4-0 v Germany\n
2014: Final, 1-0 AET v Germany\n


    </string>

    <string name="thrdslidelist">&#42; Alexis Sanchez and Gareth Bale headline a host of big names who will be absent from next summers World Cup after their countries failed to qualify for the tournament.\n&#42; Sanchezs Chile lost 3-0 to Brazil and were then relying on results, which did not go there way, in other games for qualification.\n&#42; Legendary Italian goalkeeper Gianluigi Buffon will join them watching from the sofa this summer after Italy were dumped out by Sweden.\n
    </string>
    <string name="thrdslidesquad"><b><u>GK: Gianluigi Buffon (Italy/Juventus)</u></b>\n
    The 39-year-old had planned to retire after the World Cup but he has decided to hang up his gloves following Italys play-off defeat to Sweden that reduced him to tears.\n\n<b><u>RB: Antonio Valencia (Ecuador/Manchester United)</u></b>\n
    A string of consistent performances at right-back led to Valencia being named players player of the year at Old Trafford last season but the 32-year-old could not inspire Ecuador to what would have been his third World Cup.\n\n<b><u>CB: Virgil van Dijk (Holland/Southampton)</u></b>\n
    Van Dijk has made no secret of his desire to leave St Marys but, if he is still there next June, he will miss the opportunity to showcase his talents on the biggest stage following Hollands third-placed finish in UEFA qualifying Group A.\n\n<b><u>CB: Leonardo Bonucci (Italy/AC Milan)</u></b>\n
        The defenders commitment to the cause was highlighted after playing with a broken nose in their World Cup play-off defeat to Sweden. However, his efforts proved in vain as the Azzurri crashed out.\n\n<b><u>LB: David Alaba (Austria/Bayern Munich)</u></b>\n
A winner of six Bundesliga titles and the Champions League, Alabas international career has been less illustrious with Austrias abysmal Euro 2016 campaign his only experience of a major tournament.\n\n<b><u>CM: Naby Keita (Guinea/RB Leipzig)</u></b>\n
        The Liverpool-bound midfielder will be fresh when he arrives at Anfield next summer after Guinea could not qualify from a group containing Tunisia, the Democratic Republic of Congo and Libya.\n\n<b><u>CM: Arturo Vidal (Chile/Bayern Munich)</u></b>\n
        The key midfielder, who starred in the last two World Cups, was suspended for Chiles final qualifier against Brazil and watched on powerless from Munich as his team were eliminated.\n\n<b><u>RW: Gareth Bale (Wales/Real Madrid)</u></b>\n
        It has been a positive few years for Wales but the Euro 2016 semi-finalists were pipped to a play-off spot by the Republic of Ireland, meaning Bales wait for a first World Cup goes on.\n\n<b><u>LW: Arjen Robben (Holland/Bayern Munich)</u></b>\n
        A veteran of three World Cups, Robben announced his retirement from international football shortly after scoring twice against Sweden in the final match of Hollands unsuccessful qualification campaign.\n\n<b><u>FW: Alexis Sanchez (Chile/Arsenal)</u></b>\n
        Chile suffered last-minute heartbreak as they were pushed out of a play-off place when Peru equalised against Colombia, meaning the Arsenal star will not be sprinting up the flanks for La Roja in Russia.\n\n<b><u>FW: Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang (Gabon/Borussia Dortmund)</u></b>\n
        Gabon have never qualified for the World Cup and the African countrys shortage of top-class players means talented forward Aubameyang may never have the opportunity to play at one.\n\n<b><u>Substitutes:</u></b>\n
        1. Jasper Cillessen (Holland/Barcelona)\n
        2. Gary Medel (Chile/Besiktas)\n
        3. Miralem Pjanic (Bosnia and Herzegovina/Juventus)\n
        4. Marek Hamsik (Slovakia/Napoli)\n
        5. Henrikh Mkhitaryan (Armenia/Manchester United)\n
6. Riyad Mahrez (Algeria/Leicester)\n
7. Edin Dzeko (Bosnia and Herzegovina/Roma)\n
    </string>

    <string name="secslidelist">&#42; A long journey comes to an end this week. Some nations started their road to the 2018 World Cup back in March 2015.\n&#42; In total, over 200 teams took part of the qualifying process for 31 open spots at the tournament.\n&#42; The tournament, taking place in Russia will be the first ever World Cup for Iceland and Panama.\n
    </string>
    <string name="secslidelast">
        <b>5. USA</b>\n
        USA won the CONCACAF Gold Cup for the 6th time this summer, beating Jamaica in the final 2-1, but they failed to replicate their form in the World Cup qualifiers. Called the Hexagonal, the final stage of qualifying in CONCACAF involves six of the best nations in the region playing in a 6-team group.\n\n
        The US last missed the World Cup in 1986. They still remain a powerhouse in the region, but lessons must be learned from this failure. Nothing is given in football, everything must be earned.\n\n
        <b>4. Chile</b>\n
        All the talk before the final round of matches in South America revolved around the realistic possibility of Lionel Messi and Argentina missing the World Cup. The two-time World Champions were in danger of missing the tournament for the first time since 1970, and as a finalist of the last World Cup nevertheless.\n\n
        Chile held the 4th place in FIFA rankings until July this year. They played at the Confederations Cup final at the start of July, losing only 1-0 to Germany. But that turned out to be the start of their downfall, and now, ranked 9th in the FIFA World Rankings, Chile will be the highest ranked nation to miss the World Cup.\n\n
        <b>3. Cameroon</b>\n
        Cameroon have been the most successful African nation at the World Cup. The Indomitable Lions have played at seven World Cups, one more than Nigeria. Back in 1990, lead by the legendary Roger Milla, they became the first African team to make it through to the quarter-finals.\n\n
        The qualification system is pretty cruel in Africa. There will always be a number of good sides missing out on World Cup action as only five group winners in the final round get through. Nigeria won Cameroons group with Zambia finishing second. Algeria, who reached the round of 16 at the 2014 World Cup, finished bottom.\n\n
        <b>2. Netherlands</b>\n
        The Dutch will be missing for a second consecutive big tournament. They failed to qualify for EURO 2016 with a 4th place finish in their qualification group. The Czech Republic, Iceland, and Turkey finished ahead of them and they didnt even get a chance to chase the finals ticket in the playoffs.\n\n
        The nation has been forced to still rely on the likes of Arjen Robben, Wesley Sneijder, Klaas-Jan Huntelaar and Robin van Persie, who are all near the end of their careers and far away from their prime. The next generation of players havent managed to take over the reigns of the team, without a massive drop in quality.\n\n
        <b>1. Italy</b>\n
        Italy missing from the World Cup, is no doubt, the biggest shock. They had previously only missed the 1958 edition of the tournament, which, ironically, took place in Sweden. The Swedes, this time, were the side that denied the Italians the World Cup ticket by beating them in the playoffs 1-0 on aggregate.\n\n
        Italy hasnt even made it past the group stage in the last couple of World Cups, finishing without a single win as the defending champions in 2010 and ending up 3rd behind Costa Rica and Uruguay in 2014.\n\n
        Its certainly a catastrophe for Italy to be missing the 2018 World Cup, but we can be sure that they will come back stronger in the future as a result. In Gianluigi Donnarumma, they already have a readymade replacement for Gianluigi Buffon in goal and theres some exciting talent coming up among the outfield players as well.
    </string>
    <string name="fourthslidelast">
        <b><u>Group stage</u></b>\n
<b>Thu June 14:</b> Russia v Saudi Arabia (Group A) - Moscow (Luzhniki), 4pm\n
<b>Fri June 15:</b> Egypt v Uruguay (Group A) - Ekaterinburg, 1pm\n

<b>Fri June 15:</b> Morocco v Iran (Group B) - St Petersburg, 4pm\n

<b>Fri June 15:</b> Portugal v Spain (Group B) - Sochi, 7pm\n

<b>Sat June 16:</b> France v Australia (Group C) - Kazan, 11am\n

<b>Sat June 16:</b> Argentina v Iceland (Group D) - Moscow (Spartak), 2pm\n

<b>Sat June 16:</b> Peru v Denmark (Group C) - Saransk, 5pm\n

<b>Sat June 16:</b> Croatia v Nigeria (Group D) - Kaliningrad, 8pm\n
   <b>     Sun June 17:</b> Costa Rica v Serbia (Group E) - Samara, 1pm\n

<b>Sun June 17:</b> Germany v Mexico (Group F) - Moscow (Luzhniki), 4pm\n

<b>Sun June 17:</b> Brazil v Switzerland (Group E) - Rostov-on-Don, 7pm\n

<b>Mon June 18:</b> Sweden v South Korea (Group F) - Nizhny Novgorod, 1pm\n

<b>Mon June 18:</b> Belgium v Panama (Group G) - Sochi, 4pm\n

<b>Mon June 18:</b> Tunisia v England (Group G) - Volgograd, 7pm\n
   <b>     Tues June 19:</b> Colombia v Japan (Group H) - Saransk, 1pm\n

<b>Tues June 19:</b> Poland v Senegal (Group H) - Moscow (Spartak), 4pm\n

<b>Tues June 19:</b> Russia v Egypt (Group A) - St Petersburg, 7pm\n

<b>Wed June 20:</b> Portugal v Morocco (Group B) - Moscow (Luzhniki), 1pm\n

<b>Wed June 20:</b> Uruguay v Saudi Arabia (Group A) - Rostov-on-Don, 4pm\n

<b>Wed June 20:</b> Iran v Spain (Group B) - Kazan, 7pm\n
   <b>     Thu June 21:</b> Denmark v Australia (Group C) - Samara, 1pm\n

<b>Thu June 21:</b> France v Peru (Group C) - Ekaterinburg, 4pm\n

<b>Thu June 21:</b> Argentina v Croatia (Group D) - Nizhny Novgorod, 7pm\n

<b>Fri June 22:</b> Brazil v Costa Rica (Group E) - St Petersburg, 1pm\n

<b>Fri June 22:</b> Nigeria v Iceland (Group D) - Volgograd, 4pm\n

<b>Fri June 22:</b> Serbia v Switzerland (Group E) - Kaliningrad, 7pm\n
   <b>     Sat June 23:</b> Belgium v Tunisia (Group G) - Moscow (Spartak), 1pm\n

<b>Sat June 23:</b> South Korea v Mexico (Group F) - Rostov-on-Don, 4pm\n

<b>Sat June 23:</b> Germany v Sweden (Group F) - Sochi, 7pm\n

<b>Sun June 24:</b> England v Panama (Group G) - Nizhny Novgorod, 1pm\n

<b>Sun June 24:</b> Japan v Senegal (Group H) - Ekaterinburg, 4pm\n

<b>Sun June 24:</b> Poland v Colombia (Group H) - Kazan, 7pm\n
   <b>     Mon June 25:</b> Uruguay v Russia (Group A) - Samara, 3pm\n

<b>Mon June 25:</b> Saudi Arabia v Egypt (Group A) - Volgograd, 3pm\n

<b>Mon June 25:</b> Spain v Morocco (Group B) - Kaliningrad, 7pm\n

<b>Mon June 25:</b> Iran v Portugal (Group B) - Saransk, 7pm\n

<b>Tues June 26:</b> Denmark v France (Group C) - Moscow (Luzhniki), 3pm\n

<b>Tues June 26:</b> Australia v Peru (Group C) - Sochi, 3pm\n

<b>Tues June 26:</b> Nigeria v Argentina (Group D) - St Petersburg, 7pm\n

<b>Tues June 26:</b> Iceland v Croatia (Group D) - Rostov-on-Don, 7pm\n
   <b>     Wed June 27:</b> South Korea v Germany (Group F) - Kazan, 3pm\n

<b>Wed June 27:</b> Mexico v Sweden (Group F) - Ekaterinburg, 3pm\n

<b>Wed June 27:</b> Serbia v Brazil (Group E) - Moscow (Spartak), 7pm\n

<b>Wed June 27:</b> Switzerland v Costa Rica (Group E) - Nizhny Novgorod, 7pm\n

<b>Thu June 28:</b> Japan v Poland (Group H) - Volgograd, 3pm\n

<b>Thu June 28:</b> Senegal v Colombia (Group H) - Samara, 3pm\n

<b>Thu June 28:</b> England v Belgium (Group G) - Kaliningrad, 7pm\n

<b>Thu June 28:</b> Panama v Tunisia (Group G) - Saransk, 7pm\n\n<b><u>Last 16</u></b>\n
<b>Sat June 30:</b> 1C v 2D - Kazan, 3pm (Match 50)\n

<b>Sat June 30:</b> 1A v 2B - Sochi, 7pm (Match 49)\n

<b>Sun July 1:</b> 1B v 2A - Moscow (Luzhniki), 3pm (Match 51)\n

<b>Sun July 1:</b> 1D v 2C - Nizhny Novgorod, 7pm (Match 52)\n

<b>Mon July 2:</b> 1E v 2F - Samara, 3pm (Match 53)\n

<b>Mon July 2:</b> 1G v 2H - Rostov-on-Don, 7pm (Match 54)\n

<b>Tues July 3:</b> 1F v 2E - St Petersburg 3pm (Match 55)\n

<b>Tues July 3:</b> 1H v 2G - Moscow (Spartak), 7pm (Match 56)\n\n<b><u>Quarter-finals</u></b>\n
       <b> Fri July 6:</b> Winner match 49 v Winner match 50 - Nizhny Novgorod, 3pm (Match 57)\n

<b>Fri July 6:</b> Winner match 53 v Winner match 54 - Kazan, 7pm (Match 58)\n

<b>Sat July 7:</b> Winner match 55 v Winner match 56 - Samara, 3pm (Match 60)\n

<b>Sat July 7:</b> Winner match 51 v Winner match 52 - Sochi, 7pm (Match 59)\n\n<b><u>Semi-finals</u></b>\n
    <b>     Tues July 10:</b> Winner match 57 v Winner match 58 - St Petersburg, 7pm\n

        <b>Wed July 11:</b> Winner match 59 v Winner match 60 - Moscow (Luzhniki), 7pm\n\n<b><u>Third-place play-off</u></b>\n
<b> Sat July 14:</b> St Petersburg, 3pm\n\n<b><u>Finals</u></b>\n
<b>     Sun July 15:</b> Moscow (Luzhniki), 4pm\n\n\n\n

        <b><i>All times listed BST – British Summer Time</i></b>
    </string>
     <string name="admobunitID">ca-app-pub-1629039137396721/1380257447</string>  <!--ACTUAL ADMOB UNIT-->
    <!--<string name="admobunitID">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>   &lt;!&ndash;DUMMY ADMOB UNIT&ndash;&gt;-->
    <string name="admobInterstetialunitID">ca-app-pub-1629039137396721/2118624048</string><!--ACTUAL ADMOB INTERSTETIAL UNIT-->
    <!--<string name="admobInterstetialunitID">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string> &lt;!&ndash;DUMMY INTERSTETIAL ADMOB UNIT&ndash;&gt;-->
    <string name="admobappID">ca-app-pub-1629039137396721~3459625879</string>
</resources>

